http://www.cnbmd.com/helpful-links/privacy-notice

Skip to main content
Skip to footer
Documents in Portable Document Format (PDF) require Adobe Acrobat Reader 5.0 or higher to view, download Adobe® Acrobat Reader.
Page Category:
Careers
Searching (on mobile)
Submit mobile search
Privacy Notice
Facts:  What does Shore  United Bank do with your personal information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
Transaction history and credit history
Investment experience and account transactions
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Shore United Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information:
For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Does SHORE UNITED BANK share? Yes Can you limit this sharing? No
For our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services to you
Does SHORE UNITED BANK share? YesCan you limit this sharing? No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Does SHORE UNITED BANK share? YesCan you limit this sharing? No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your transactions and experiences
Does SHORE UNITED BANK share? NoCan you limit this sharing? We don't share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness
Does SHORE UNITED BANK share? NoCan you limit this sharing? We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
Does SHORE UNITED BANK share? NoCan you limit this sharing? We don't share
To limit our sharing:
Call toll free
1-877-758-1600 and ask for Customer Service
Email us at Privacy@ShoreUnitedBank.com, or
Visit any branch location
Please note:
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we provided or sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?
Call toll free 1-877-758-1600
What we do:
How does Shore United Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
Our employees are bound by our Code of Ethics and policies to access consumer information only for legitimate business purposes and to keep information about you confidential.
How does Shore United Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
open an account or apply for a loan
make deposits or withdrawals from your account or enter into an investment advisory contract
give us your contact information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes
information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
Definitions:
Affiliates - Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Shore United Bank has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates - Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Shore United Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing - A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners may include financial institutions such as insurance companies and financial product or service marketing service.
Other important information:
Other Privacy Statement
We occasionally use third parties such as Facebook and Google to serve you targeted ads based on behavioral data that they collect on websites that you visit across the internet. Technology such as cookies and web beacons are used to collect this data. The data collected is not personal information and does not identify you as an individual. You can limit the collection of this data by modifying your browser settings and ad settings on various platforms, including: Chrome, Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Facebook’s Ad Settings, and Google’s Ad Settings.
Privacy Notice Last Updated 11/2020
Accordion Toggle for
Accordion Toggle for
Accordion Toggle for
Accordion Toggle for
Accordion Toggle for
Accordion Toggle for
Accordion Toggle for
We welcome you to sign up for our e-newsletter with valuable insurance information and other helpful boating tips.
×Close login modal
Please select a login.
Banking
Investments
If you see this message, the login screen did not load.
Please contact Shore United Bank's Online Banking Customer Service directly for assistance at 888-820-6840.
Please select an investments login option.
